newsbeatsocial.com 2016-06-06

# Privacy Policy - NewsBeat Social

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. 
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. 
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. 
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**LEGAL LEGEND:** An offering statement relating to securities of NBS has been filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission but has not yet become qualified. These securities may not be sold nor may offers be accepted prior to the time the offering statement becomes qualified. You may obtain a copy of the most recent version of the preliminary offering circular by clicking on the following link: <https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1661424/000114420416085843/v432385_partiiandiii.htm>

No money or other consideration is being solicited in connection with this information, and if sent in response, will not be accepted. No offer to buy securities can be accepted and no part of the purchase price can be received until an offering statement on Form 1-A is qualified pursuant to Regulation A of the Securities Act of 1933, as amended, and any such offer may be withdrawn or revoked, without obligation or commitment of any kind, at any time before notice of its acceptance given after the qualification date. Any person's indication of interest involves no obligation or commitment of any kind. No offer to sell any securities, and no solicitation of an offer to buy any securities, is being made in any jurisdiction in which such offer, sale or solicitation would not be permitted by law.
